NVIDIA Q3 2025 10-Q Financial Results: Total revenue increased 20% year-over-year to .1 billion. Data center revenue was .2 billion, up 25% YoY, driven by AI and cloud computing demand. Gaming revenue was .8 billion, down 5% YoY due to market saturation. Professional visualization revenue was .6 billion, up 8% YoY. Automotive revenue was .5 billion, up 15% YoY. Net income was .9 billion, up 35% YoY. EPS was .52, up 40% YoY.
