Tesla Q3 2025 10-Q Financial Results: Total revenue increased 15% year-over-year to .5 billion, driven by growth in automotive and energy storage segments. Automotive revenue was .2 billion, up 12% YoY. Energy generation and storage revenue reached .8 billion, up 25% YoY. Services and other revenue was .5 billion, up 18% YoY. Net income attributable to common stockholders was .1 billion, compared to .8 billion in Q3 2024.
